<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<course id="6" contextid="43">
  <shortname>ProfGuide</shortname>
  <fullname>L2A: Professional's Guide to Educating Adults</fullname>
  <idnumber></idnumber>
  <summary>&lt;p&gt;This course introduces teachers to the Learning to Achieve Professional Guide is useful resources for educators to better understand learning disabilities of adults. It was developed as a companion piece for the Learning to Achieve training. The Professional Guide explains the characteristics of adults with learning disabilities and provides intervention strategies for teaching these students. Because the intervention strategies in the guide are relevant to any individual with learning disabilities, practitioners can use the guide for a large spectrum of students.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This course takes approximately 1 hour to complete.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;---&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Please Note:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This course contains Adobe Flash content. To view the content, you must have the Adobe Flash Player installed. You can download and install the Flash Player from &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="http://www.adobe.com/products/flashplayer/"&gt;http://www.adobe.com/products/flashplayer/&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From our experience, Adobe Flash content is best viewed in the Google Chrome web browser.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Unfortunately, the Flash Player cannot run on all operating systems. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are using an iPad, an iPhone, or an Android device running Android Jelly Bean or later, you may not be able to view the Adobe Flash content, and will need to take the course using a different device.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
  <summaryformat>1</summaryformat>
  <format>topics</format>
  <showgrades>1</showgrades>
  <newsitems>0</newsitems>
  <startdate>1367640000</startdate>
  <marker>0</marker>
  <maxbytes>20971520</maxbytes>
  <legacyfiles>0</legacyfiles>
  <showreports>0</showreports>
  <visible>1</visible>
  <groupmode>0</groupmode>
  <groupmodeforce>0</groupmodeforce>
  <defaultgroupingid>0</defaultgroupingid>
  <lang></lang>
  <theme></theme>
  <timecreated>1367607232</timecreated>
  <timemodified>1387549769</timemodified>
  <requested>0</requested>
  <enablecompletion>1</enablecompletion>
  <completionnotify>0</completionnotify>
  <numsections>1</numsections>
  <hiddensections>0</hiddensections>
  <coursedisplay>0</coursedisplay>
  <category id="2">
    <name>Learning Disabilities</name>
    <description></description>
  </category>
  <tags>
  </tags>
</course>